Dammit, more magic?!
Those damn vampires!
We have to murder them
before they invoke their ma-
Flames, oh flames...
Ice, oh ice...
I have a message from the commander!
The Lapelico army has already been
completely decimated!
The victory of the Komari unit
is clear as day!
See that, you inferior beast-folk?
Guess we're having those beast-folk's blood
made into liquor for our victory party, eh?
It's too early for celebration.
Victory has yet to be decided.
Rejoicing in a situation where the enemy
may have some sort of ace up their sleeve
is quite low-class.
Shame on you.
This current battle is the first campaign
for us, the Mulnite Empire.
We absolutely will not be beaten.
Am I right, Your Excellency Terakomari?
Yes, you are correct, Caostel.
Listen up, everyone!
I am Terakomari Gandesblood!
I've been a professional shut-in
for the past three years.
The Vexations of a Shut-in Vampire Princess
The Shut-in Vampire Goes Outside
I constantly think about
how the world is so irrational.
15 years ago, I was born into
the Gandesblood clan,
one of the most noble clans
in the Mulnite Empire.
The Gandesblood family has passed down
the title of imperial general for
the last thousand years.
I tried hard to meet the expectations
of those around me...
But I quickly got frustrated.
I was lacking in aptitude
in every possible way.
First of all, I can't use magic.
Secondly, my athletic ability is non-existent.
And third, I'm short.
It's clear to me the reason why I am
burdened by this trifecta of misfortune.
Even though I'm a vampire,
I can't drink blood.
It's a necessary source of nutrition
for growth, but I just can't stand it.
The smell, the sight;
I hate everything about it.
In a plethora of ways, my life has
only ever been full of bitter memories.
Power is everything in vampire society...
I swore to be a peace-loving,
righteous vampire,
and decided to shut myself in.
Wha?
The Mulnite national emblem...
Why?
Lady Terakomari, good morning.
Wh-who are you?!
Why are you in my room?
I should have introduced myself sooner.
I am Villhaze.
I belong to the Mulnite Imperial Army.
My rank is junior lieutenant, third division.
I've taken up a new job as Lady Terakomari's
personal maid, starting today.
Still...
Pardon my saying so,
but this room is quite the mess.
What are you here for? Is it money?
Please don't be afraid.
I am an ally, Lady Terakomari.
Hey, Villhaze or whatever...
Wait right here a sec.
We have no time for that.
Come with me now to the imperial court.
Let me go! I have to go pee!
This is no time to pee.
Please listen to me.
I'm going to pee myself!
Is that what you want?!
Please listen to me while you pee yourself.
That's pretty perverted, don't you think?!
There's no time for this,
so please do as I say.
No! You're gonna kidnap me!
Beauty like mine only comes around
once ever hundred million years, you know!
Is that something you can say about yourself?
Let her go, Vill.
Oh, Komari!
Are you hurt?
Ou...ouch. Gonna die...
More importantly, Dad!
What is her deal?!
This is Vill, and she'll be your
personal maid starting today.
I don't need a maid.
Especially one this scary...
Even so, this has been decided
by the Her Majesty.
The empress? What do you mean?
Let me explain that to you.
Lady Terakomari.
Do you know of the Seven Crimson Lords?
Where's this coming from?
I mean, yes, I know of them.
The Seven Crimson Lords...
They're seven super strong,
most fearless fighters among vampires
who lead the Mulnite Army.
And you have become one of them,
Lady Komari.
Huh?
The other day, when I asked you
"How about you start working soon?"
and you replied:
Well, I don't mind working
if I get the throne.
I was so moved!
I went and reported it to
the empress the other day,
and I said "Please, pass
the throne to Komari."
Are you nuts?!
I did my very best for you.
I then emphasized to a
thoroughly pissed empress
just how much of a prodigy you are
while still having a beauty
that only comes around once every
hundred million years.
And then, the empress said "Interesting."
This is NOT interesting!
Thus, the empress entered
a contract with you,
and that's how you were appointed
as a Crimson Lord.
Well, I have no recollection of
that contract, though.
She snuck in last night.
Who did?
The empress.
Huh?
While you were sleeping, Lady Terakomari,
she kissed you, thus sealing the contract.
Whaaaaaat?!
Well, hello! Welcome Komari!
And you are just as darling as always!
We are simply overjoyed to see you!
It's an honor, but... um, Your Majesty...
you're a little close for comfort,
don't you think?
By the way, We would like to
massage your boobs, may We?
Your Majesty, please lighten up with the jokes.
She will cry.
It's just a joke!
We are the type who takes emotions
into great consideration.
Until you are in the mood for it,
We will massage your boobs.
You kissed me, right?
How funny!
Honorifics don't suit you!
From here on, you should treat Us as
a friend you have known for 10 years!
I've never had a single friend before.
Now then, Terakomari Gandesblood.
I called on you for no other reason
than to tell you that...
It's time for the segment to explain the points
of note upon becoming a Crimson Lord!
Bam bam! Woo-hoo!
What's up with that picture?!
The Crimson Lords have one condition
under which they must operate:
Once every three months, they must
go to war with another nation and win.
Furthermore, once the 100th war is won,
you can gain candidacy
to become the next empress.
That's an impossible hurdle to clear.
On the other hand, if you
continue to lose in these wars...
Will I get the chop?
Yes! You'll explode and
that head will definitely fly!
You have got to be kidding me!
Please don't crush my expectations!
Don't worry.
You are in charge of around 500 men
from the 7th unit of the army.
However, it is teeming with those who will
certainly aim to murder their superior
upon learning they are weak.
Then aren't they basically my enemies?!
How can I not worry?!
Vampires are the type that desire
the chance to move up in the world.
Komari...
You're actually weak, yes?
Yes, super weak!
Dying is that thing where like...
it's really painful, right?!
It hurts more than bashing a pinky finger
in the corner of a dresser, doesn't it?!
Then you don't want to die?
Of course I don't!
Then it must be kept secret.
No matter what happens,
you must behave as the absolute strongest
while in front of your troops.
The maid next to you will be
your support with that.
Please consider me capable, Lady Komari.
We shall make sure to fool them all.
I feel nothing but anxiety...
You won't try to overthrow me, right, Vill?
Of course not.
I love you more than anyone else
in the universe, Lady Komari.
A bold-faced lie.
We just met today.
It suits you quite well, Lady Komari.
I-I suppose it does!
Well, I may not look it,
despite how I look now,
beauty like mine only comes around
once ever hundred million years, you know!
Anything I put on looks amazing on me.
That's wonderful, you're so pretty.
In that case, how about we do a fashion show
starring you when we get back?
Like hell we will, that's dumb!
Now, Lady Komari.
The troops you will command
are waiting for you.
Y-yeah...
This door must seriously weigh like
a million tons or something...
It can't possibly, your run-of-the-mill
vampire should be able to open it.
Well, sorry for being so abnormally weak!
You've got this, Lady Komari.
Hey! Don't just stand there!
Help me!
Ah, it's ope-
Die, Your Excellency!
Lady Komari, are you all right?
I-I-I-I-I..
I'm-I'm-I'm...
There, there. Good girl.
Wh-what am I gonna do?
They'll probably find out
that I'm incredibly weak...
No need to worry.
You've triumphed over an insolent rebel.
Vill, is he...
He is dead.
He's dead?!
Oh no, how did this happen?
Maybe I should leave some flowers...
All a moron like him needs
is spit on his corpse.
More importantly, let's go.
Your troops are waiting.
R-right...
Am I really welcoming subjugation?
Can I make it out of here alive...?
Your Excellency, I am convinced.
To think that of all people, Yohan Helders,
Used to be Yohan
who is especially hot-blooded even among
this 7th unit, would be killed in one strike...
I can handle a vampire of his caliber
with a single pinky finger!
Whoa, she's joking, right?
No way...
This new commander's savage...
By the way, as a child,
Lady Komari slayed a hundred vampires
with a single pinky finger.
If Lady Komari got serious,
it would be possible for her to slaughter
everyone one here in five seconds.
Damn you! I don't need your input here!
Anyone would be able to
figure out that's a lie!
Hey! Put that thumb back down!
You didn't help me out here at all!
Ahem, more importantly, is it all right
if I greet the whole troop now?
Yes, ma'am! You may do as you please!
The 7th Unit...
No, Commander Komari's troop members
are sincerely and impatiently waiting for
Your Excellency's greeting.
Everyone!
I am the new Shichiguten,
Terakomari Gandesblood!
Now that I have become your commander,
understand that you will
no longer live the tranquilili...
Lady Komari was so nervous
she flubbed up her speech.
Well? Adorable, isn't she?
Just kick me while I'm down, why don'tcha?!
Back me up!
Understand that you will no longer have
the tranquil life you have been living!
From here on, every day will be war!
The flow of blood will be endless!
The carnage will be daily!
But be at ease, all you need to do
is silently follow me!
Never let the thought of stupid things
like overthrowing me cross your mind,
and just be faithful to the sweet and mighty
Terakomari Gandesblood!
I give you my word!
If you follow me,
for as long as war rages on,
I will allow you to enjoy
boundless daily pleasure!
Our first campaign is against
the Lapelico Kingdom's army,
and our first battle is with
the nobodies led by monkeys!
Simply winning is not enough!
We will be known all over the world!
They will know the truth that I,
Terakomari Gandesblood,
am the vampire who will become
conqueror of the world!
I have an urgent message!
Lieutenant Bellius has killed
the enemy general!
Our army has won!
I mean, if I had been on the battlefield,
I could've torn the enemy general
to pieces in three seconds, though.
Three seconds?
No, my mistake! One second, just one!
I'd stomp every last one of them
in one second!
Whoa!
Komarin! Komarin! Komarin! Komarin!
Komarin! Komarin!
Well done, everyone!
However, the beasts are not our only enemies!
The Warblades of the Gerra Arka Republic,
and the Sapphires of the Haku-Goku
Commonwealth will learn of my strength!
Also, uh...
The Heavenly Paradise and
The Enchanted Lands.
Right!
The Heavenly Paradise and The Enchanted Lands
will be thoroughly trounced!
Yeah!
Yes, all you have to do is
stay loyal to the all mighty me!
Under all circumstances,
follow me faithfully and obediently!
Do not think of overthrowing me!
Never think of that!
All you have to do is
believe in and protect me!
Yeah!
Come, let us go forth and conquer,
my dear soldiers!
Over there lies the vivid,
blood-red color of glory!
Komarin! Komarin! Komarin! Komarin!
How did this happen?
Pardon me, do you have a moment?!
I'm Melka Tiano of
the Six Nations Newspaper!
Lady Terakomari Gandesblood,
is it all right if I interview you?!
S-sure, ask me anything, but can you
start by giving me some space?
Thank you so much!
Hey!
What were the circumstances that led
to you becoming a Crimson Lord?!
What relationship do you have
with Her Majesty?!
What kind of food do you like?!
Is it true that you killed a hundred vampires
with your pinky finger?!
Do you have any lovers?
Who was your first kiss?
Enough, get away!
The strong do not speak with words!
But that may cause problems for you,
so I'll tell you just a bit!
What I will be doing from now on
is simply boundless domination!
Namely, Terakomari Gandesblood...
will annihilate all of the commanders
of the five other nations in battle,
and spread the word of the might of
Mulnite over the entire world!
You got that?!
W-wow...
By the way, my favorite food
is omelette rice!
That is all!
Now THIS is a Crimson Lord.
The very strongest of the vampires...
Thank you, gods...
I am blessed to be born in the same
generation is Her Excellency!
Hey! This way, please!
Yes, very cute! Wonderful!
What is the point of this?
Haven't died in a long time.
Sure is rough, huh...
In this world, a war where you
live or die doesn't exist.
Each one of the six nations in this world
possesses its own "Dark Core,"
a super high grade ritual article
that produces boundless magic.
As far as the influence of
the Dark Core's magic is concerned,
however deep the wound,
however tragic the death it was,
after a certain amount of time passes,
one will completely recover.
As such, the place I'm standing now
is the "Dark Core Zone."
It's the special area where the Dark Cores
of the six nations overlap perfectly,
and the wars among us all occur
exclusively in this area.
What do you think, Lady Komari?
This is the so called "entertainment war."
I cannot stand how absurd this is.
Good morning, Lady Komari.
Y-you! Why are you here?!
Ah.
Why are you naked?!
Ah!
Get some clothes on now!
Lady Komari, please have a look
at today's newspaper.
See, your picture from yesterday is on it.
What are you talking about?!
Now is not the time for newspaper... hm?
"New Shichiguten Bursts Onto the Scene,
Will Make the Entire World
Into Omelette Rice"
"I love omelette rice.
I will murder the commanders
of the other five nations,
"haphazardly dump ketchup on them,
and make them look like omelette rice
with the insides scooped out."
This is pure and simple fake news!
It's already totally agitating
the other nations, isn't it?!
Correct. According to the article,
a chimpanzee killed yesterday said:
"She won't get away with this!
Sooner or later we will
thoroughly disgrace you!"
And, they were shamelessly making
death threats in the national paper.
Nooooooo!!!!
Please relax.
I will protect your chastity, Lady Komari.
You're the one I'm most worried about!
Lady Komari, about today's plans...
Aaaaah, I can't hear you!
Today is my day off!
If you're going to stay under the covers forever,
I have some ideas of my own.
Hmph, if you come even one step closer to me,
I'm gonna cry so hard I hiccup!
"The Strawberry Milk Formula."
"I thought I wanted a love
like strawberry milk.
Sweet and mild, without the thrill
that teasingly torments the tongue,
eternally warm, gentle;
a love like sunshine.
Stop iiiiiiit!
I found it when I was rummaging
through your trash can.
Nevertheless, it is still a surprise
to see a love story.
Anyways, if you continue to
skip out on your duties,
I will distribute this story throughout
the imperial court, are you okay with that?
With the writer's name attached, of course.
What?
Lady Komari, are you listening?
I'll do whatever you say...
I'm begging you, please don't tell anyone.
Do not worry, I will not be doing that.
Th-thanks, Vi-
Ahhh!
Smells so, so good!
If I'm sniffing something, I should go
for her directly and not her pillow!
Ah, I want to ascend to Heaven enraptured by
this sweet scent of strawberry milk!
She is the creep of the century!
I'm exhausted.
How long has it been since I've
talked to someone this much?
Try to fight back at least a little, c'mon!
Stop...
I don't like it, it hurts...
I will never allow it!
A Sudden Insurrection
"A Sudden Insurrection."