Well?
What am I doing today?
Lady Komari, today you'll have a meeting
with those executive-level oaficers.
Hey, did you just say "oaficers"?
Don't you mean "officers"?
Now, let's get those clothes changed.
Whoa, hey! Wait!
I don't wanna! Stop! Whoa!
I don't need to take off the panties!
And so, getting stright to the point,
I have a question for you all.
How would you like to proceed from here on?
Fight and a fightin', fight fight fightin'...
Perpetual war.
Lieutenant Bellius Hund Cerbero
Demoted on murder charges
I want to witness Your Excellency's success.
Lieutenant Caostel Conto
Demoted on suspicion of kidnapping a young girl
A rap battle with Your Excellency yo!
Ooh yeah!
Captain Mellanconcey
Demoted on failed attempt to blow up the palace
O-of course...
But for now, you would like
to have war, right?
That is correct.
Now then, we shall continue on to the rewards
from Her Excellency Terakomari.
What?
Her Excellency greatly appreciates
your success in the previous battle
against Lapelico Kingdom,
and she has decided to
repay you for your actions.
Your Excellency is so perfectly photogenic.
But, if I had any say in it, then...
I would increase your variety of clothing!
All right, that's the death penalty!
Death penalty for you!
I do think it suits you extremely well, though.
Just get to dying!
I will... withhold my request for now.
Okay.
Yeah, rap battle!
Yeah!
It's Bloodbath Rapper Mellaconcey,
all my peeps suffer when I sing a high key!
You're the only one vibin'
with my flow so sick,
it's me and you and dead bodies,
all up on our 'fits!
Yeah!
Yo! Yo!
I'm General Komarin,
super strong, can't get no higher!
A wise lil' ruler in this dark empire!
So who's your number one,
who are you fond of?
Just ask anybody, they all get my love!
Yeah!
The Vexations of a Shut-in Vampire Princess
A Sudden Insurrection
The person known as Terakomari Gandesblood
is a tremendous mystery.
And what is that?
A classified document from the imperial court.
The imperial academy raid which caused
an uproar throught the empire
three years ago...
Those details are noted here...
Hey, why do you have something like that?
The culprit in that case is Her Excellency.
What?
According to this part...
There were 30 deaths on the academey's side,
and 70 deaths from the imperial army's
third unit who were sent to take control...
they were all killed with one pinky finger.
By the way, as a child Lady Komari slayed
a hundred vampires with a single pinky finger.
Wait... the culprit in that incident
should be someone else.
The guilty party was switched.
To tell the truth, this part that says
"Terakomari Gandesblood"
is being reported as "Millicent Bluenight"
who has nothing to do with this.
I don't understand.
I don't either, but...
Three years ago, Her Excellency Terakomari
caused a massacre the likes of which
we have never seen before,
is what this means.
Hey, you over there, this place is off-limits
unless you work for the palace.
If you don't want to be killed...
The palace guards are surprisingly steadfast.
I thought I could just go into
the empress' palace and kill her, but...
Thanks to the wall-defense magic,
I couldn't get in.
You... are you trying to take out the empress?
I'll kill her at some point.
But now is not that time.
Oh? Well then, why did you come here?
It's not anything major,
just here to check on things a bit.
I read in the paper that Terakomari Gandesblood
has become a Crimson Lord...
Is that true?
How optimistic to think that magic would work!
Is that all you've got?
Above you!
What are you even looking at?!
None of you can hinder me.
Just learning that made all this worth it.
Give my best to Terakomari, 'kay?
See ya!
She's going after Her Excellency.
What do we do?
There's nothing we can do.
If only I could get a reward coupon for
foot-licking from Her Excellency!
We will move on our own initiative
and handle her!
That sounds good.
You want a coupon for
a foot-licking reward too?!
No! I agree with taking the initiative!
Good morning, Lady Komari.
Oh, it's you Vill. Morning.
But why are you dressed like that?!
It's weird!
You're really good at wearing
embarassing things, huh?!
Do you have any shame at all?!
I do not.
Don't admit to it!
How am I supposed to react to that?!
About today's affairs...
I don't care, tell my subordinates
I'm pretending to be sick.
I feel it would be awkward to tell them
you were feigning illness.
More importantly, are you sure you want that?
You have important plans
to choose your beast today.
Huh?! By beast, you mean THAT beast?!
Now then, Lady Gandesblood.
These are the stables for the beasts.
Wow...
There they are, the beasts!
And there are so many!
To tell the truth, I've kind of longed
for a magical beast!
Come here.
Ah! You can't have that one, Lady Gandesblood!
That one is...
Aww, there you go!
Excuse me, what is that dragon?
That is a mizuchi native to
The Enchanted Lands,
and it is one of the highest classes
among all of the beasts.
That tickles!
and it is one of the highest classes
among all of the beasts.
But, well, it has a intense preference
for young girls,
and it can't open it's heart to
anyone but a young girl.
I see, that is certainly an explanation
I can understand.
Okay, I've decided!
This one will be my partner!
Now, let's go, Bucephalus!
Let us ride with the wind!
Yo! It's a mock battle but get
blown to smithereens! YEAH!
Tch! Terakomari Gandesblood!
I will get my revenge...
I'll make sure of it!
Outta the way, outta the way, outta the waaay!
Huh?
Stop!
Huh? I'm floating?
Eh?
Oh dear, Lady Komari...
I tell you daily to stop with
the dramatic dismounts, and yet...
Vill...
I'm no' tanking you.
You seem to be tongue-tied.
Sh...shuddup.
Hurry and put me down.
Don't say that. Just a little longer...
Hey...
Controlling a magical beast at that speed
is just as I'd expect from her.
I thought she'd die after falling off but...
Controlling a magical beast at that speed
is just as I'd expect from her.
she's got some serious guts.
J-jus' pu' me down.
Right away.
My goodness!
Is that you, Your Excellency?
A pleasure to see you.
Caostel, how you doin'?
I am doing wonderfully, thank you.
Every member of the Komari unit
is giving their all in training.
Oh? I'm please ta hear dat.
Yes, please take part in the exercises as well,
Your Excellency, by all means!
What're you sayin'? If I take par'
ev'yone will die o' my sickness.
Certainly, that simpleton died
before challenging you to a battle.
Huh?
That piece of refuse was run over
and killed by your mount.
Long live Her Excellency!
Long live murderers!
Purge all traitors!
I'm not dead yet you boneheads!
Die, little girl!
Oh... I'm gonna d-
She dodged?!
Eh?!
Whaaaat?!
Wow, what poise!
Her Excellency is magnificent.
It's as if she's a matador!
I'm dizzy...
Damn it!
Move outta the way!
My eyes! My eyes!
S-sorry...
Lady Komari!
Let's hit him hard right here.
This is what happens when you defy me!
Next time, I'll gouge out your eyeballs
and those other balls too,
so make sure you're ready for that!
Y-you little...
You really got me good...
You'll pay for this!
Terakomari Gandesblood!
I challenge you to a duel!
A duel?
Komarin! Komarin! Komarin!
Your Excellency!
Beat the hell out of that loser!
Koma-tan is so great!
Lady Komari, can you hear me?
How is it going?
Obviously extremely crappily!
You can do it, this is where
you must stand firm.
Vill, can I...
Can I survive this and go home?
Have you forgotten?
Just because you're killed
does not mean you'll die.
I know that! But it hurts!
And it's hot! And I'll suffer!
Please relax.
As long as I am here, it is completely
unlikely that you will die in a duel.
Leave it all to me.
I will bring the glory of victory to you.
Really?
T-Terakomari...
T-today I will make sure you b-burn!
I filled his meal with poison.
You did this?!
What's wrong, Your Excellency?
Gonna burn, burn, burn you all up...
G-gonna send you to the hospital.
You're the one who should go to the hospital!
The hell you say?!
G-g-gonna murder...
What do I do about this?!
This is like a horror movie
that's unsuitable for kids!
Hey Vill!
Okay, Lady Komari. Use magic.
What?!
If I could do something like that
I wouldn't be struggling right now!
No, just act like you're using it.
On my signal, snap your fingers like you're
making a big show of it for everyone.
Huh?!
Here we go.
3, 2, 1...
Okay, now!
What was that magic?
She opened a hole under
her opponent's feet from that far?!
That's the advanced magic skill
"Kingdom Crumbler."
But I couldn't feel the slightest
flow of magical power...
In short, this means Her Excellency can
also use power-concealing magic skills.
Ah yes, the advanced magic skill
"Lacquered Wings," huh?
Lacquered Wings
Wow! Your Excellency is so mighty!
What was that?
I dug a pit last night.
Amazing, Your Excellency!
How is that possible?!
By the way, this arena is set up
with pits in 52 places.
Absolutely do not move, Lady Komari.
You call that magic?
I'm not playing around, you damn fraud!
Hey Vill, where are the pits?
Unfortunately, there are no pits
on the straight line
connecting you and Lieutenant Helders.
Why not? You dug a ton of them, right?!
I can only attribute this to bad luck.
Burn!
Hey, time out, time out!
Vill, can't we do something
with the snap again?!
No, it's too late for that.
Whaddaya mean too late?!
Like my life is over?! You've gotta be-
Landmines.
Eh?
L-landmines?
Last night, I buried about 69 of them.
You didn't think this plan through very well...
Now Lieutenant Helders has
safely met his maker.
You have won, Lady Komari.
Uh, yeah, I guess...
Now you've done it...
I'm gonna catch you,
burn your clothes off,
and make you do the fire dance naked...
Huh? He's dead?
Lady Komari, declare your victory.
R-right...
Sorry.
The rebel is dealt with!
Yeah!
Oh, oh yeah! Oh!
Komarin! Komarin! Komarin!
Say Vill, I feel like I'm deceiving everyone.
It isn't just a feeling, you actually
are deceiving everyone.
I thought I was gonna die...
Maybe I should thank her too.
I want you to express that with your body
and not your words if at all possible,
so may I proceed to embrace you?
S-stop it, you're such a perverted maid!
Now, Lady Komari, you must
prepare to bathe with me.
Wait! Don't massage me there!
And you're hurt, aren't you?!
I only have blisters.
Tomorrow they will be magically healed.
Tell me about your injury.
I can't.
Then this is an order, tell me about it.
There were pits there to kill
Yohann Helders, right?
Yeah.
I dug them all with a shovel.
You did that manually?!
Deadly poison is the only magic I can use.
I-I see...
I apologize for showing you
something so unsightly.
It's not unsightly at all!
You worked really hard for my sake, Vill.
If you weren't there, I'd be dead right now.
I'm, well... grateful to you for that.
So... don't try to hide the injuries
you suffered for my sake.
I mean, I should share that
sort of injury with you.
So...
In any case, thank you.
That's what I mean, do you get it?
I do.
Huh? You do?
I understand that Lady Komari loves me.
Well, whatever.
But let me ask you...
Why do you cling to me so much?
It's a little creepy.
Because you have a beauty that only
comes around once every million years.
Well I know that.
But that's not what I mean.
I'm curious if there's some other,
more special reason.
I've commited a crime.
I know that too.
You sexually harass me like crazy.
Damn it!
Damn you, Terakomari Gandesblood!
You loathe her that much?
That little girl?
You're Lieutenant Helders of
the imperial army, right?
Who are you?
I'm Millicent...
of the sublime Inverse Moon.
Say.
Want to do business with me?
An invitation to that
perverted Empress's party?
Yes. She said it's to congratulate you
for your success and the like.
Huh. Will I get paid overtime,
or have a make-up holiday or...
Your Excellency, what should we do?
You also...
Er, I mean, do you dislike this sort of thing?
To be frank, yes.
I have come to live a life that has
no relation to the upper class.
No need to be so down on yourself.
There's no doubt that your military
achievements as a member of
the imperial army are the results
of your hard work.
That's something to be proud of, Bellius.
Y-Your Excellency...
Welcome, Sweet Komari!
Are you enjoying yourself?
Oh, stop. Today's festivities are informal.
Komari, We wouldn't mind you
calling Us "Ren-chan," not at all!
By the bye, Komari, how is your job
as a Crimson Lord going?
Like I can tell you that.
No need to ask, eh?
In the short time since you've
taken up your post,
you've defeated four other nations
excluding The Enchanted Lands,
I've never seen a Crimson Lord quite like you.
I was just lucky, no other explanation for it.
This is a party to celebrate your achievements.
Oh, here, how do you like
the 100% blood juice?
Ah, you don't like blood.
Actually, We are feeling relieved.
Three years ago you were
shut away in your room,
and it must have been difficult
to re-enter society like that,
but looks like your father's gamble
was a success.
Gamble?
Yes, he bet that you would leave your room
if you were forced to be a Crimson Lord.
Huh?!
Komari, you aren't alone anymore.
You have subordinates you can rely on,
and Komarists all through the empire...
Just like Us, there are plenty of people
that love you dearly,
so no matter what happens, don't fall into
despair like you did three years ago.
Well then, enjoy the party!
Terakomari.
Mind having a chat with me too?
The Darkness of the Shut-in Vampire Princess
"The Darkness of the Shut-in Vampire Princess."